United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5817 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm
1904-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America (UBC)
UBC Local 502
5817 mf
0.22 cubic feet
4 mmicrofilm reels
Minute books, microfilm.
5710658
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 06, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America; UBC Local 502, Canandaigua, NY.
5710658
- Vol. 1-4 (1904-1944) (Reel 1)
- Vol. 1, 1904-1910; 1 (Reel 1)
  Scope and Contents
  7/12/1904 - 6/14/1910
- Vol. 2, 1910-1922; 2 (Reel 1)
  6/28/1910 - 12/19/1922
- Vol. 3, 1923-1931; 3 (Reel 1)
  1/2/1923 - 12/15/1931
- Vol. 4, 1932-1944; 4 (Reel 1)
  1/5/1932 - 6/6/1944
- Vol. 5-7 (1954-1975) (Reel 2)
- Vol. 5, 1954-1966; 1 (Reel 2)
  8/4/1954 - 7/6/1966
- Vol. 6, 1966-1975; 2 (Reel 2)
  8/3/1966 - 4/29/1975
- Vol. 7, 1975; 3 (Reel 2)
  5/19/1975 - 12/3/1975
- Negative copy of Reel 1. (Reel 3)
- Negative copy of Reel 2. (Reel 4)